Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Research materials and projects
  - Publication projects, 1992-2012
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Attendees, lists of (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Notes (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Paper (Frauke Heard-Bey), research notes (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Paper (Frauke Heard-Bey), Arabic translation of (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Program (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Scholarly and public policy works: monographs, periodicals, papers, 1972-2018
  - Publications: monographs, reports, and general
    - Afaaq Athaqafah wa Turath (Juma Al-Majid Center for Culture and Heritage, Dubai), Issue No. 1, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Central Veterinary Research Laboratory, Dubai. New Observations on Camels and their Milk, by Ulrich Wernery, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Central Veterinary Research Laboratory (Dubai): brochures and pamphlets, 2014 and undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Chatham House: The United Nations and the Gulf War, 1990-1991: Back to the Future? Paul Taylor and A.J.R. Groom (RIIA Discussion Papers, 38), 1992 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Accessions list, October 1971 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: "Der europaisch-arabische Dialog: Entwicklung und Zwischenbilanz," Ursula Braun (Orient, Sonderdruck nr. 18), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Deutsche Hochschulschriften über den modernen islamischen Orient = [German theses on the Islamic Middle East], by Detlev Finke, Gerda Hansen, Rolf-Dieter Preisberg., 1973 (Volume 125)
      Z3013 .F55 1973
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Periodicals inventories, 1967-1969 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - ECSSR: Emirates Center for Strategic Studies & Research Major Activities, 1994/1995 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - ECSSR: The Three Occupied UAE Islands: The Tunbs and Abu Musa (Booklet), 2005 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - ECCSR: Thurow, Lester. al-Mutanāṭiḥūn: al-maʻrakah al-iqtiṣādīyah al-qādimah bayna al-Yaban wa-Ūrūbbā wa-Amrīkā, 1994 (Volume 126)
      First edition. Arabic translation of Lester Thurow's "Head to head: the coming economic battle among Japan, Europe, and America."
    - ECSSR. With United Strength: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, The Leader and the Nation (Press Release Ver.), by Andrew Wheatcroft. Emirates Center for Strategic Studies and Research. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Fatḥī, Mamdūḥ Anīs. al-Imārāt ilá ayn?: istishrāf al-taḥaddiyāt wa-al-makhāṭir ʻalá madá 25 ʻāman al-qādimah, 2005 (Volume 127)
      DS247.T8 F38 2005
    - Ibrahim, Muhammad. al-Majlis al-Waṭanī al-Ittiḥādī bi-Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah, 1972-1986 (Volume 128)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). A Study of International Migration in the Arab Region [outlines of project], April 1977 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - International Migration Project(University of Durham). Movements of Migrant Labor from part of the North of the Sultanate of Oman, May 1977 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). Country Case Study: The Sultanate of Oman (Part One), July 1977 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). Country Case Study: Kuwait (Part One), July 1977 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). Aspects of the Demography of the Sultanate of Oman, Sept. 1977 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). Country Case Study: Libyan Arab Jamahiriya, July 1978 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - International Migration Project (University of Durham). A Summary of Provisional Findings: Empirical Patterns, Past Trends and Future Developments, Nov. 1978 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Mack, Rosamond E. Bazaar to Piazza: Islamic Trade and Italian Art, 1300-1600. (Berkeley: University of California Press, 2002). (Volume 129)
      NK959 .M267 2002
    - Montigny-Kozlowska, Anie (French anthropologist, based in Qatar): reprints of articles by, 1982-2005 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1976-1977 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1977-1978 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1981-1982 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Nah- und Mittelostverein, e.V.: Tätigkeitsbericht, 1989-1990 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - National Avian Research Center. Annual Report, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - The Problem of Management Accountability in the Public Sector of the United Arab Emirates (UAE): Case Study of Two Public Sector Organisations, doctoral dissertation, University of Hull, by Juan Salem Ali, 2001 (Volume 130)
      JQ1844.A58 A45 2001
    - Tammam, Hamdi. Zayed bin Sultan al-Nahayyan: the Leader and the March (Abu Dhabi: the Author), 1981 (Volume 139)
      DS247.T88 T3513 1981
    - UNDP. Arab Human Development Report. Creating Opportunities for Future Generations, 2002 (Volume 131)
      HN766.A15 A73 2002
    - UNDP. Arab Human Development Report. Building a Knowledge Society, 2003 (Volume 132)
      HN766.A15 A73 2003
    - UNDP. Arab Human Development Report. Toward Freedom in the Arab World, 2004 (Volume 134)
      HN766.A15 A73 2004
    - Wernery, Ulrich; Kinne, Joerg; Schuster, Rolf Karl. Camelid Infectious Disorders (Paris: World Organisation for Animal Health), 2014 (Volume 135)
      SF997.5 C36 2014
  - Publications: serial
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 11, No. 3, July 1997 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 12, Nos. 1-3, 1997-1998 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 13, Nos. 1-3, 1998-1999 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 14, Nos. 1-3, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 15, No. 2; Vol. 16, No. 3, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 18 (3 issues), 2004 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 20, No.2; Vol. 21, No. 1; Vol. 22, No. 3, 2006-2007 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 23, Nos. 1-3, 2007-2008 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 24, Nos. 1-3, 2008-2009 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - BRISMES Newsletter (British Society for Middle East Studies), Vol. 25, Nos. 2-3, plus documents, 2010-2011 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient). Vols. 3-4, February - September 1996
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 5-6, February - September 1997
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 7-8, February - September 1998
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 9-10, February - September 1999
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 11-12, February - August 2000
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 14, August 2001
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 15-16, June - December 2002
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 18, December 2003
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 22, December 2005
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 23-24, August - December 2006
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 25-26, August - December 2007
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 27-28, August - December 2008
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 30, December 2009
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vols. 31-32, August - December 2010
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 33/34, June 2012
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 35, January 2013
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 38/39, June 2015
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 42/43, August 2017
    - DAVO-Nachrichten (Deutsche Arbeitsgemeinschaft Vorderer Orient), Vol. 44/45, September 2018
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: Mitteilungen / Bulletin, February 1972 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Deutschen Orient-Instituts. Mitteilungen. Nummer 10, 1977. "Entwicklungsprobleme der arabischen Erdoelstaaten." (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Deutsches Orient-Institut: "Orient," indexes, 1970-2001, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 1, March 1977 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 2, June 1977 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 3, October 1977 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 4, March 1978 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 5, July 1978 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 7, April 1979 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), July 1979 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 9, November 1979 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 10, March 1980 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 11, July 1980 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin (Abu Dhabi), No. 12, November 1980 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin, 1-6 (bound, with indices), 1977-1978
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin, 7-12 (bound, with indices), 1979-1980
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin, 13-18 (bound, with indices), 1981-1982
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin 19-24 (bound, with indices), 1983-1984
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin 25-30 (bound, with indices), 1985-1986
    - Emirates Natural History Group Bulletin 31-36 (bound, with indices), 1987-1988
    - Memória (Arquivo Nacional da Torre do Tombo, Portugal), Issue no. 1, April 1989 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 3, no. 1, July 1998 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 4, nos. 1-2, December 1999 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 5, Nos. 1-2, December 2000 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 6, Nos. 1-2, September 2001 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-2, March - November 2002 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 8, Nos. 1-2, March - November 2003 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Occident and Orient: Newsletter of the German Protestant Institute of Archaeology in Amman, Vol. 9, Nos. 1-2, 2004 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Orient [come up with list of what is on the shelf, keep on shelf]
  - Conference proceedings, lectures, and symposia
    - Abu Dhabi: 250 years of development. Symposium sponsored by Emirates Heritage Club and Sultan bin Zayed Centre for Culture and Media, Fairmont Bab al Bahr Hotel, Abu Dhabi. Conference program, 19-20 December 2011 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage. International Heritage Day: Heritage, Visibility and Transmitting it to Future Generations, Abu Dhabi, 18-19 March 2009 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage. Fourth International Heritage Symposium, "Heritage and Education: A Future Vision", March 29 - April 1, 2010 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Amman Conference: Regional Implications of the Gulf War (bound volume with program, participant list, selected papers), June 16 - 20, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Business International Conference: "Saudi Arabia and the GCC: Corporate Issues for Survival and Growth" (Sheraton Abu Dhabi), September 24-26, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Centre for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi: Bedouin Society in the Emirates. Conference program., 26 February - 1 March 2005 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Crown Prince Court. Research and Studies Department. Oil and Regional Developments in the Gulf. Abu Dhabi (conference program), 15-16 November 1997 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Crown Prince Court. Heard, David G., OBE. "The Place of the Gulf in the International Energy Market: the UAE in Context." Paper presented at "Oil and Regional Developments in the Gulf" conference, Abu Dhabi., November 1997 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Crown Prince Court. "The Environment: Issues for the Gulf." Welcome speech by H.H. Sheikh Saeed bin Saif al Nahayan, Director of Research and Studies Division. Abu Dhabi. [spiral bound, also contains papers and slides by other speakers, and handwritten notes by F. Heard-Bey], 24-25 October 1998 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Crown Prince Court. Research and Studies Department. International Symposium on Globalization: Trends, Implications and Responses. Conference program., 12-13 November 2000 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Crown Prince Court. Research and Studies Department. International Symposium on Regional Implications of the Fallout from the War in Iraq. Intercontinental Hotel, Abu Dhabi. [conference program, with F. Heard-Bey's handwritten notes in back folder flap], 11-12 October 2003 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - ECSSR: The Gulf: Challenges of the Future. 9th Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - ECSSR: Arab Media in the Information Age. 10th Annual Conference, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - ECSSR: Current Transformations and their Potential Role in Realizing Change in the Arab World. 11th Annual Conference, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - ECSSR: Arabian Gulf Security: Internal and External Challenges. 12th Annual Conference, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - ECSSR: The Gulf Oil in the Aftermath of the Iraq War: Strategies and Policies. 9th Annual Energy Conference, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - ECSSR: The Gulf Oil and Gas Sector: Potential and Constraints. 10th Annual Energy Conference, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - ECSSR: Gulf Oil and Gas: Ensuring Economic Security. 11th Annual Energy Conference, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - ECSSR: Globalization in the 21st Century: How Interconnected is the World? 10th Specialized Conference, April 2007 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - ECSSR: The German Role in Developing European Socio-Political Dialogue with the Arab World, Ambassador Dr. Gunter Mulack (Lecture 237), January 19, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - ECSSR: Conflict Resolution in the Post-Cold War World: Implications for Iraq, bu General Sir Michael Rose, ECSSR (Lecture 238), 23 Feb. 2004 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - ECSSR: Russian Relations with Europe and the US: Implications for Global Security, by Vitaly V. Naumkin, Emirates Center for Strategic Studies and Research (Lecture 251), 29 March 2005 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - ECSSR: Challenges and Opportunities in the Middle East: An American Perspective, by Dr. Richard N. Haass, Emirates Center for Strategic Studies and Research (Lecture 253), 5 May 2005 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - ECSSR: Iran's Nuclear Program and its Impact on the UAE and the Gulf Region, by Dr. Richard Russell, Emirates Center for Strategic Studies and Research (Lecture 270), 10 Jan. 2007 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - ECSSR: The Israel Lobby and US Foreign Policy, by John Mearsheimer and Stephen Walt, Emirates Center for Strategic Studies and Research (Lecture 293, Arabic translation of text), 16 June 2008 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - ECCSR: Itihad al-Imarat: bein al-madi wa al hadr wal al-mustaqbal [symposium], November 28, 2006 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Education Without Borders 2003: World Forum Panel Discussions, February 23, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Education Without Borders, World Forum, 2003. Program. [Oversize]
    - Education Without Borders 2003: Speaker presentations [abstracts, with notes by F. Heard-Bey], February 23, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Education Without Borders 2003: Yearly Calendar (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Education Without Borders 2005: International Student Conference (Program Booklet), 19-21 February 2005 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Emirates Foundation: Tawteen Symposium (MENA Learning and Leadership), Abu Dhabi. Program, speaker bios, list of participants, handwritten notes by F. Heard-Bey, February 2007 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Folklore and Oral History of the UAE and the Arab Gulf States (United Arab Emirates Heritage Club), March 2000 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - GCC Heritage and Oral History Conference: Sixth Conference on Heritage and Oral History, "Zayed and Heritage through History", October 2018 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Muḥāḍarāt al-mawsim al-thaqāfī: li-ʻām 1395/1396 (Wizārat al-Iʻlām wa-al-Thaqāfah) = Lectures of the Cultural Season, 1975-1976 (Volume 136)
      DS36.4 .M833 1976
    - NATO-UAE Relations and the Way Forward in the Istanbul Cooperation Initiative. Emirates Palace [Hotel], Abu Dhabi. [Folder with various brochures: conference program, speakers biographies, fact sheet on Istanbul Initiative, invitation to F. Heard-Bey], 27 October 2009 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Perspectives on the Middle East, 1983. Proceedings of a conference. Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy and Middle East Institute (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Scientific Papers: First International Conference and Exhibition on the Preservation of Architecture, in Theory and Practice. Municipality of Dubai [Arabic], March 14 - 16, 2004. (Volume 140)
      CC135 .M83 2004
    - Sorbonne University-Abu Dhabi: The Oasis: Ecosystems and Their Value for Heritage and Tourism, International and Multidisciplinary Colloquium, December 2014 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - UAE. Center for Documentation and Research. Proceedings of the Fourth Seminar of the Centres and Institutions Concerned with Gulf and Arabian Peninsula Studies, held in Abu Dhabi, November 1979 (Volume 138)
      DS222.92 .H33 1979
    - UAE University, UNDP and FAO: Proceedings of The Date Palm Global Network held in Al Ain - UAE University, April 2002 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - University of Exeter, Centre for Arab and Gulf Studies. Symposium on Higher Education in the Gulf: Problems and Prospects (six papers), 10-12 July 1995 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Telephone directories, 1971-2017
  - ADTT Telephone Directory Emirate of Abu Dhabi, February 1971
  - ADTT Telephone Directory Emirate of Abu Dhabi, October 1971
  - ADTT Telephone Directory Emirate of Abu Dhabi, April 1972
  - [Abu Dhabi government telephone directory], 1972
  - [Abu Dhabi government telephone directory], 1973
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1982-1983
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1984-1985
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1985-1986
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1987
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1989
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1990
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1992
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, 1993
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Abu Dhabi Edition, 1995
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Abu Dhabi Edition, 1995
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Abu Dhabi Edition, 1997
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Abu Dhabi Edition, 1999
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Abu Dhabi Edition, 2004
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages, 1980
  - Abu Dhabi Classified Business Listing Yellow Pages, 1982-1983
  - Abu Dhabi Classified Business Listing Yellow Pages, 1983-1984
  - Abu Dhabi Classified Business Listings Yellow Pages, 1984-1985
  - Abu Dhabi Classified Business Listings Yellow Pages, 1985-1986
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages - Commercial Directory, 1987
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1988
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1989
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1990
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1991
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1992
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1993
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Emirates Telecommunications Corp., Ltd.), 1995
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages [?], 1998
  - Abu Dhabi Yellow Pages (Etisalat), 2002
  - UAE Business Pages. Hawk Media, 2003
  - Etisalat Yellow Pages Abu Dhabi Edition, 2007
  - Etisalat Yellow Pages Abu Dhabi Edition, 2008
  - Etisalat Yellow Pages Abu Dhabi Edition, 2013
  - Etisalat Yellow Pages Abu Dhabi Edition, 2017
  - United Arab Emirates Telephone Directory, Mobile Edition (Etisalat), 2004
  - Website & Telefax Directory (Etisalat), 2004
  - Telephone Directory, Mobile Edition, 2006